國家歷史博物館
華盛頓
它在這。
There it is.
據我們所知昨晚，
What we know is that last night,
華盛頓國家博物館
here at the National Museum in Washington D.C.,
一件臭名昭著的藝術品水晶頭骨
an artifact known as one of the infamous crystal skulls
被偷。
was stolen.
這顯然不是第一個水晶頭骨被偷。
This is apparently not the first crystal skull to be taken
並且，根據博物館館長所說，
and, according to the museum's director,
過去兩年已有至少六個頭骨。
there have been at least six skulls in the past two years
從博物館和和全球收藏品
from museums and collections from across the globe
不明原因消失。
that have disappeared under nefarious circumstances.
來自CNB新聞，約書亞奧德爾的報道。
For CNB News this is Joshua O'Dell.
水晶頭骨
庫斯科，秘魯
塞納。
Senor.
薩呂。
Salut.
我認為它是真實的。
I assume it's authentic.
毫無疑問。
Without a doubt.
你看，我的僱主會很失望。
You see, my employer would be very disappointed
如果它被證明是偽造的。
if it turned out to be a forgery.
你是怎麼搞到這件藝術品的？
How did you obtain the artifact?
考慮到我的業務性質，
Given the nature of my business,
你可以理解為什麼我不能透露這些細節。
you can understand why I cannot reveal such details.
運輸和銷售此類文物
There are strict regulations about the transport
大概有嚴格的規定。。
and sale of such antiquities.
再說一次，我的僱主非常希望
Again, my employer would be very-
你的老闆希望要麼我出價要麼他不想要。
Your employer either wants what I have to offer or he does not.
在這種情況下，我有其他買家要見。
In which case, I have other buyers to meet.
你沒必要行駛200英里到安第斯山脈。
You didn't travel 200 miles up into the Andes
如果你有其他買家。
if you had other buyers.
那麼我們準備好談生意了？對不？
Then we are ready to do business? Yes?
當您聯繫您的代表，
When you contacted our representative,
您的留言有一定的購買價格。
your message included a certain purchase price.
我想那數額比較公道。
And I believe the amount was more than fair.
因為確實我的僱主。
As does my employer.
你有你的項目？
Do you have the item with you?
我不是一個傻瓜，米切爾先生。
I'm not a fool, Mr. Mitchell.
但就在附近。
But it is close by.
帶錢了沒？
Do you have the money?
我也不是一個傻瓜。
I'm not a fool either.
跟我走。
Follow me.
要不要點下？
You going to count it?
沒必要。
That will not be necessary.
那麼，我的朋友，
Then, my friend,
我們交易完了。
we're finished here.
你擔心的事情已經發生了。
What you have feared has come true.
我擔心什麼？
And what have I feared?
他在收集頭骨。
He's gathering the skulls.
他明白那聚集一起可以擁有權力。
He understands that together they have power.
誰？
Who?
財主。
The rich man.
富人。
The infidel, Hadden.
他是一個老人，
He's an old man,
一個受權力夢驅使的無知的人。
a foolish man who is driven by dreams of power
來自於頭骨。
derived from the skulls.
他是個危險的人，你不懂嗎？
He is a dangerous man, you understand?
是的，我明白，但真正的危險是。
Yes, I understand, but the real danger is that
沒有第十三頭骨
without the thirteenth skull
將沒有法來控制它們。
there will be no way to control them.
其他12個可能變得不穩定。
The other twelve could become unstable
並造成大規模破壞。
and cause massive destruction.
這就是兄弟會給你這個任務的原因。
This is why the brotherhood has given you a task.
會有殺戮。
There will be bloodshed.
你是在徵求我的同意還是我的意見？
Are you asking me for my approval or my opinion?
我不需要你批准。
I don't need your approval.
那麼我的觀點是沒必要暴力，
Then my opinion is that there is no need for violence,
只是阻止他。
he just needs to be stopped.
傻瓜才信一個富人會被阻止。
You're a fool to believe a rich man can be stopped
而不是通過殺戮。
without bloodshed.
我知道你有一個使命，我祝你好運，
I understand you have a mission and I wish you good luck,
但別讓你的憤怒害了你，侯賽因。
but don't let your anger poison you, Hussein.
korallgrottan洞穴，瑞典
檢查所有設備。
Check all your equipment.
確保我們有足夠長的繩子？
You sure we have enough rope?
你肯定東西在那嗎？
You sure there's something down there?
我不會做。
I wouldn't be doing this
如果我不確認東西在下面。
if I didn't think there was something down there.
你知道我是怎麼想海拔，泰利。
You know how I feel about heights, Terry.
別擔心。
Don't worry about it.
我何曾讓你失望？
Have I ever let you down?
3，4次，上衣。
Three, four times, tops.
登山是我的強項。
Climbing is my business.
你只需要別抱怨了。
You're just gonna have to suck it up.
看看那個，哥哥。
Look at that, bro.
去容易。
Go easy...
邊上。
...over the lip.
呼！
Whooo!
穩住，哥哥。
Go steady, bro.
瞧那個！
Look at that!
耶。
Yeah.
不會吧。
Holy cow.
是這裏。
It was here.
是嗎？你怎麼這麼肯定？
Yeah? How can you be so sure?
這是他筆記本筆記本裏最後參觀的地方。
This is the last place in his notebook that he visited.
以後的生活與他的癡迷第十三頭骨。
After living with his obsession with the thirteenth skull
這些年來，
For all these years,
我們最終會發現它。
we're finally going to find it.
你先。
After you.
你是考古學家。
You're the archaeologist.
好了，你是冒險家。
Well, you're the adventurer.
妻子會認為與該。
The wife would argue with that.
她說，我是一個榮耀的導遊。
She says I'm a glorified tour guide.
洙導遊。
So guide.
好吧，哥哥。
Ok, brother.
沒有GPS所有我靠老地圖。
There's no GPS down here so I'm working off old maps.
它的下跌這個洞穴另一對夫婦百米。
It's down this cave another couple hundred meters.
你肯定爸爸在這裏？
You sure dad was here?
他描述了這條隧道。
He describes this tunnel.
我們都知道，
For all we know,
什麼是留給他的是躺在附近這兒的地方。
what's left of him is lying around down here somewhere.
我們應該為他找不管它是什麼，他是後。
We owe it to him to find whatever it was he was after.
你準備好了？
You ready for that?
我已經準備好了。
I'm ready for that.
你準備好了？
You ready for that?
我猜是。
I guess so.
我們會沒事的。
We'll be alright.
如果你這麼說，哥哥。
If you say so, brother.
你先。
After you.
哈登A.G總部
奧地利維也納
一切準備好了？
Is everything ready?
是的，他們一直在等待著你的到來。
Yes, they've been awaiting your arrival.
什麼問題？
Any problems?
我呢？沒有。
Me? No.
傢伙我得到這個從可能有不同的意見。
Bloke I got this from might have a different opinion.
為什麼？
Why's that?
我不認為你想知道的是，馬洛裏小姐。
I don't think you want to know that, Ms. Mallory.
該實驗室已建成八個級別的地下。
The lab has been built eight levels underground.
你期待的麻煩？
You expecting trouble?
讓我們希望不是。
Let's hope not.
留神。
Watch yourself.
這邊。
This way.
注意腳下。
Watch your feet.
哎，
HEY,
看來，我們發現了一些東西。
looks like we found something.
確實，不是嗎？
We did, didn't we?
你先。
After you.
老人優先。
Age before beauty.
是他嗎？
Is that him?
你不認為他會錯過這一刻，你呢？
You didn't think he'd miss this moment, do you?
哈登先生？
Mr. Hadden?
米切爾先生。
Mr. Mitchell.
幹得好
Bravo .
謝謝你，先生。
Thank you, sir.
我不知道還能活多久，
I don't know how much time I may have left,
所以我們不要再浪費時間了。
so let's not waste any more of it.
正常嗎？
Is that normal?
同時，據我們所知，
Well, as far as we're aware,
這是第一次的頭骨團聚
this is the first time the skulls have been reunited
人類歷史上。
in the history of mankind.
發生了什麼？
What's happening?
有聲波振動16赫茲。
There's sonic vibration at sixteen hertz.
我覺得有些不舒服。
I feel a little sick.
我不知道他們是如何做的，
I don't know how they're doing it,
但這些東西都產生自己的磁場。
but these things are generating their own magnetic field.
這是不可能的。
That's not possible.
告訴他們。
Tell them that.
什麼好說的？
What's it say?
週四晚上是女士之夜。
Thursday night is ladies night.
所有的女人都會被錄取，無蓋。
All women will be admitted, no cover.
所有飲料2束縛。
All drinks two shackles.
什麼？
What?
我不知道。
I have no idea.
但他們在爸爸的書。
But they're in dad's book.
12不同的符號。
Twelve distinct symbols.
你怎麼能知道，聰明的傢伙。
How can you know that, smart guy
如果你不知道他們說什麼。
if you don't even know what they say.
好吧，我並不需要能夠把它們翻譯。
Well, I don't need to be able to translate them
為了知道是阿卡迪亞，
in order to know that is Acadian,
這是埃及，
this is Egyptian,
那些在這裏我真的不認識。
those over here I don't really recognize.
這一點，這看起來前哥倫布。
This, this looks pre-Colombian.
最有可能的瑪雅。
Most likely Mayan.
南美？
South American?
地獄的是這裏做什麼？
What the hell's it doing here?
正是。
Exactly.
預巴比倫，蘇美爾，我們已經得到了埃及，瑪雅可能。
Pre-Babylonian, Sumerian, we've got Egyptian, possibly Mayan.
我的猜測是它的十二個不同的組。
My guess is it's twelve different groups
代表不同的早期文明。
representing a different early civilization.
有啥第十三呢？
So what's the thirteenth for?
我的意思是，你已經有了12組符號，
I mean, you've got twelve sets of symbols,
12文明古國，12頭骨。
twelve ancient civilizations, twelve skulls.
如果真的有第十三個頭骨，
If there really is a thirteenth skull,
那是什麼呢？
what's that about?
是，我的朋友，是一個很好的問題。
That, my friend, is a good question.
我真的不知道在這一點上，
I really have no idea at this point,
但我敢肯定，我會找到了。
but I'm sure I'm gonna find out.
我想我會嘔吐！
I think I'm gonna puke!
是的，它的頻率。
Yeah, it's the frequency.
某些調製引起噁心。
Certain modulations cause nausea.
七赫茲，它可能會導致你的身體來分開。
At seven hertz, it can cause your body to come apart
在核級。
at a nuclear level.
已關閉的規模！
Is off the scale!
我們會失去它。清理房間。
We're gonna lose it. Clear the room.
清理房間！
Clear the room!
讓他們離開那裏！
Get them out of there!
我們試圖激活關閉
We've tried to activate the shut-down-
只是做我告訴你！
Just do what I tell you!
哇。
Whoa.
你摸了什麼？
What'd you touch?
沒！我什麼都沒做！
Nothing! I didn't do anything!
我告訴你不要碰任何東西！
I told you not to touch anything!
哇。
Wow.
北約空軍基地
薩拉戈薩,西班牙
紅色代碼。
Code Level Red
上校，脈衝消散。
Colonel, the pulse has dissipated.
我們有一個核爆炸的任何報告？
Do we have any reports of a nuclear detonation?
消極的，先生。
Negative, sir.
什麼？
Nothing?
沒有，先生。
No, sir.
沒有。
Nothing.
衛星或地震。
Satellite or seismic.
那麼到底是什麼呢？
Then what the hell was it?
我們挑upan電磁爆，
We've picked up an electro-magnetic burst,
而且似乎它起源於維也納。
and it appears it's originated in Vienna.
維也納？
Vienna?
奧地利維也納？
Vienna, Austria?
作為莫扎特和巧克力？
As in Mozart and chocolates?
這是正確的，先生。
That's correct, sir.
好吧。
Alright.
手錶的指揮官，把我們帶回了黃色。
Commander of the watch, take us back to yellow.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
電磁脈衝不只是憑空出現的。
Electra-magnetic pulses don't just come out of nowhere.
瞭解，先生。
Roger that, sir.
主要。
Major.
告訴參謀長聯席會議他們會知道那是什麼，當我知道這是什麼。
Tell the joint chiefs they'll know what it was when I know what it was.
這一切恢復正常，除了。
All of it is back to normal except...
頭骨仍產生一個字段。
The skulls are still generating a field.
正是。
Exactly.
他們保持穩定的時刻，按鈕
They're holding steady for the moment, but-
你看到發生了什麼。
You saw what happened.
是的，當然。
Yes, of course.
好了，我們知道，頭骨具有獨特的磁性特質。
Well, we knew that the skulls possess unique magnetic qualities.
如果你的理論是正確的，第十三應該有─
If your theory was correct, the thirteenth should have-
本來應該能夠控制他人。
Should have been able to control the others.
理論是沒有問題的。
The theory isn't the problem.
的問題是，這不是第十三顱骨。
The problem is that that wasn't the thirteenth skull.
你不是在責怪我，他的公雞了，是嗎？
You're not blaming this cock-up on me, are you?
到底誰應該去責備這個不折不扣的災難，
Who exactly should we blame for this unmitigated disaster,
先生。米切爾？
Mr. Mitchell?
先生。 hadden-
Mr. Hadden-
你擔保的真實性，你發表了偽造。
You vouched for the authenticity and you delivered a forgery.
先生。哈登，我真的很抱歉，但我的老本行。
Mr. Hadden, I'm really sorry but in my line of work
人有一種傾向，說謊。
people have a tendency to lie.
是這樣的，先生。米切爾？
Is that so, Mr. Mitchell?
我本來打算由您的聯繫人所提供的資料，先生。
I was going on information supplied by your contacts, sir.
是的，你應該審核這些信息，對嗎？
Yes, and you were supposed to vet this information, am I correct?
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
你可能已經和審訊的第一章。
You could have gone and interrogated the chap
誰給你的，但是這將是太困難的，
who gave it to you, but that would have been too difficult,
不是嗎？
wouldn't it?
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
每個人都會犯錯。
Everybody makes mistakes.
謝謝你，哈登先生。
Thank you, Mr. Hadden.
永遠不要犯同一個錯誤。
Don't ever make another one.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
去找真正的頭骨。
Go and get the real skull.
和他一起去。
Go with him.
沒多少時間了。
There isn't a lot of time.
我想這死了的兩個男人的家庭。
I want the families of those two men who died
得到妥善照顧。
taken care of.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
一個奇怪的電子干擾。
A strange electrical disturbance
昨晚震動了奧地利維也納。
rocked Vienna, Austria last night
與停電。
with power outages...
市中心有一次大爆炸。
...There was a large blast in the centre of the city...
目前，駐法國的北約部隊。
...Coming in now, the French NATO troops
處於高度戒備狀態。
high alert following...
BMP
...BMP...
任一個城市或政府官員的任何單詞。
...Any word from city or government officials...
對此拒絕置評。
...Have refused to comment on this...
政府官員是什麼造成了這種。
...Government officials on what has caused this...
引爆原子武器。
...Detonation of an atomic weapon...
似乎是一個高調的會議。
...What seems to be a high-profile meeting
與總統。
with the president...
我是梅拉妮·考克斯，維也納在線，和我們呆在一起。
I'm Melanie Cox, live from Vienna, stay with us.
哇。
Wow.
酷。
Cool.
小心你碰的，它會殺了你。
Be careful what you touch, things could be booby-trapped.
對不起，兄弟。
Sorry, bro.
這是爸爸的戒指。
It's dad's ring.
你是對的。
You were right.
不，不，不要去碰它！
No, no, don't touch it!
什麼也我只是告訴你嗎？
What did I just tell you?
我沒有碰任何東西！
I didn't touch anything!
對不起，對不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
讓我們在這裏了！
Let's get out of here!
去！
Go!
快點，約翰！
Hurry, John!
好的，來吧。
Ok, come on.
夾在。
Clip in.
你呢？
You in?
- 所有設置。- 確定。
- All set. - Ok.
遙控器。
Remote.
鬆弛超出。
Slack is out.
來吧。
Come on.
怎麼了？
What's wrong?
它不工作。
It's not working.
沒有。
No.
給我你的，我們會一起去。
Give me yours, we'll go together.
夾在。
Clip in.
來吧，來吧！
Come on, come on!
對不起。
I'm sorry.
在那裏，你在做什麼？
What're you doing??
特裏！
Terry!
對不起，哥哥。
I'm sorry, brother.
我們能做到這一點起來，加油！
We can do this together, come on!
特裏，不這樣做！
Terry, don't do this!
這是唯一的辦法。
It's the only way.
對不起。
I'm sorry.
特裏！
Terry!
我愛你，男人。
I love you, man.
特裏！
Terry!!
我哥哥總是陪伴著我。
My brother always stood by me
儘管他並不總是相信。
even though he didn't always believe in
我在做什麼。
what I was doing.
我想這就是我會最想念他的。
I guess that's what I'll miss most about him.
LUH 。
Luh...
我要感謝大家的光臨今天。
I want to thank everybody for coming today
和你付尊重。
and paying your respects.
這將意味著很多我的兄弟。
It would mean a lot to my brother.
謝謝。
Thank you.
媽媽，我想念我的爸爸。
Mommy, I miss my daddy.
我知道你想念你的爸爸，親愛的。
I know you miss your daddy, sweetie.
我想念你的爸爸，太。
I miss your daddy, too.
如果有什麼以往任何時候都需要，
And if there's anything ever that you need,
你問你的叔叔約翰，好不好？
you ask your Uncle John, ok?
好吧，叔叔約翰。
Ok, Uncle John.
我猜它運行在家庭。
I guess it runs in the family.
那是什麼？
What's that?
沒有身體，沒有棺材。
No body, no casket.
勞拉，我很抱歉。
Laura, I'm so sorry.
我。
I...
這不是你的錯。
It wasn't your fault.
他是我的小兄弟。
He was my little brother.
我應該保護他。他沒有跟我。
I should have protected him. He didn't have to come with me.
他抬頭看向你。
He looked up to you.
他會跟著你的任何地方。
He would have followed you anywhere.
- 溫斯頓教授？ - 不是現在，拜託。
- Professor Winston? - Not now, please.
- 你好，教授溫斯頓。 - 女士。
- Hello, Professor Winston. - Ladies.
你介意告訴我這是什麼？
Do you mind telling me what this is?
它像什麼？
What's it look like?
它看起來像我的課被取消了。
It looks like my classes have been cancelled.
這就是它說，是的。
That is what it says, yes.
你會關心澄清？
Would you care to elucidate?
我不明白為什麼。
I don't understand why.
我想你的兄弟去世後。
I thought after your brother's death
你可能需要一些時間。
you might want some time.
嗯。
Hmm.
不，我不需要時間。
No, I don't need time.
我只是需要找回我的教學。
I just need to get back to my teaching.
它不是想像中的那麼容易，約翰。
It isn't quite that easy, John.
你是部門負責人，格裏。
You're the head of the department, Gerry.
你為什麼不只是讓那麼容易嗎？
Why don't you just make it that easy?
我是誰必須回答的部門負責人。
I'm the head of the department who must answer
該學院的院長，
to the president of the college,
誰又將有回答董事會。
who in turn has to answer to the board of trustees.
又哪裏受托人必須做任何這樣？
And what do the trustees have to do with any of this?
你是誰告訴這些孩子之一。
You're the one who told these kids
一些神離棄水晶頭骨的故事。
about some god forsaken crystal skull story.
傑拉德，你現在跟我開玩笑吧？
Gerald, are you kidding me now?
它只是一個理論。
It's just a theory.
你和我都知道，。
You and I both know that.
這是正確的，理論。
That's right, a theory.
這不正是我們試圖在這裏做？
Isn't that what we're trying to do here?
幫助孩子為自己著想？
To help kids think for themselves?
學校最大的捐助者之一反對。
One of the school's largest donors objected.
我的雙手被縛。
My hands are tied.
所以現在的捐助者決定的課程？
So now donors dictate curriculum?
他們要拉資金，約翰。
They were going to pull the funding, John.
所有的資金。
All the funding.
我們談論50教師職位。
We're talking fifty faculty jobs.
好吧，好吧。
Ok, alright.
告訴我是誰。
Tell me who it is.
我會告訴他們，也許我可以說服他們，如─
I'll talk to them, maybe I can convince them, if-
沒有，有沒有說服他們。
No, there's no convincing them.
他們的想法是由。
Their minds are made up.
你是一個世界級的考古學家約翰，
You're a world class archaeologist, John,
和罰款的學術。
and a fine academic.
你必須知道，這樣的事情。
You had to know that something like this
會趕上你遲早。
would catch up with you sooner or later.
約翰。我真的很遺憾。
John. I am truly sorry about this.
我也是。
Me too.
他一直在那裏很長一段時間。
He's been in there a long time.
給它一個幾分鐘。
Give it a few more minutes.
又過了幾分鐘，我們將有一個血淋淋的大腿舞。
A few more minutes and he'll have a bloody lap dance.
好吧，這就是它。
Alright, that's it.
離開它的任何時間更長，他將絕對砸了。
Leave it any longer and he's going to be absolutely smashed.
看到光明的一面。你可以隨身攜帶他出去。
Look on the bright side. You can carry him out.
我不會讓他扔了我的新衣服。
I'm not going to have him throw up on my brand new suit.
來吧。
Come on.
如果你有一支筆，我就簽給你。
If you've got a pen, I'll sign it for you.
如果你是幸運的，哪天它會是值得的東西。
If you're lucky, some day it'll be worth something.
實際上，你的僱主非常感興趣。
Actually, our employer is very interested
與您討論吧。
in discussing it with you.
好吧，
Alright,
什麼是他或她的名字？我會做出來給他 -
what is his or her name? I will make it out to he or she-
威廉·哈登。
William Hadden.
H-A-D-D-E-N 。
H-A-D-D-E-N.
威廉·哈登？
William Hadden?
非常富有的技術傢伙？
The very wealthy technology fellow?
是啊，這會是一個。
Yeah, that'd be the one.
現在什麼，他想與我的書？
Now what would he want with my book?
不是你的書，隊友。
Not your book, mate.
你。
You.
我呢？
Me?
讓我們只說對他有很深的那一刻，
Let's just say for the moment that he has a very deep,
個人興趣在題材。
personal interest in the subject matter.
好了，也許你應該告訴先生。哈登。
Well, perhaps you should tell Mr. Hadden
他是稍微誤導。
that he's slightly misguided.
水晶頭骨是一個理論。
Crystal skulls are a theory.
顯然不是一個非常好的。
Apparently not a very good one.
哦，我的'。
Oh s my'
那麼，如果我們告訴你。
Well, what if we told you
這是一個有點不僅僅是一個理論。
it was a little more than just a theory.
我想說的是，你們需要再喝一杯。
I'd say that you guys need another drink.
並通過你們我的意思是我。
And by "you guys" I mean me.
請。
Please.
這是我。
It's me.
是的，他們都在裏面，現在。
Yes, they are inside now.
我明白我的使命。
I understand my mission.
他們不會獲得第十三頭骨。
They will not acquire the thirteenth skull.
這聽起來像你要我作出聲明。
It sounds like you want me to make a statement.
精。
Fine.
它將被處理這樣。
It will be handled that way.
所以我想你不會要我簽書？
So I take it you don't want me to sign the book?
先生。哈登願意陪我們到維也納。
Mr. Hadden would like you to accompany us to Vienna.
他想和你談談本人對頭骨。
He would like to talk to you in person about the skulls.
維也納聽起來可愛。
Vienna sounds lovely.
但不幸的是我有一些同學，
But unfortunately I've got some students,
講座參加到。
lectures to attend to.
真的嗎？
Really?
因為我們聽說你已經被賦予了休假。
Because we heard you've been given a sabbatical
從你的教學義務。
from your teaching obligations.
哦，你聽說過嗎？
Oh, you heard about that?
先生。哈登是一個減輕你。
Mr. Hadden was the one that relieved you
這些義務。
of those obligations.
現在，他為什麼還要那樣做？
Now why would he want to do that?
他有更大的魚魚苗，不是嗎？
He's got bigger fish to fry, no?
他要你來維也納。
He wants you to come to Vienna
討論你和你父親的一生的工作。
to discuss you and your father's life's work.
他認為這將是更好，如果他有你的。
He thought it would be better if he had your
讓他出來！
Get him out!
上樓梯！去！
Up the stairs! Go!!!!
誰是這傢伙，為什麼他在你拍攝的？
Who was that guy and why was he shooting at you?
他沒有拍攝我，他瞄準了你！
He wasn't shooting at me, he was aiming for you!
他是什麼？
He was what?
第十三頭骨仍然在那裏。
The thirteenth skull is still out there
還有人誰願意做任何事情來阻止它。
and there are people who would do anything to stop it
從被發現。
from being found.
包括像那傢伙的狂熱分子。
Including fanatics like that guy.
那麼，如果哈登希望我一心一意，
Well if Hadden wanted my undivided attention,
他肯定現在有吧。
he certainly has it now.
走，走！
Go, go!
我想在維也納脈衝更新。
I want updates on the Vienna pulse.
還是有電磁信號。
There's still an electro-magnetic signal
從位置，先生正在生成。
being generated from the location, sir.
什麼是源？
What's the source?
沒有辦法告訴沒有，先生。
No way to tell yet, sir.
信號強度保持穩定，
Signal strength is holding steady,
散熱的跡象。
no signs of dissipating.
所以他們仍然能夠產生另一個脈衝的？
So they're still capable of generating another pulse?
是的，上校。
Yes, colonel.
如果第二個越強，
If the second one is stronger,
他們可以歐洲黑掉一半。
they could black out half of Europe.
在維也納地上通知地方當局。
Notify local authorities on the ground in Vienna.
我想組裝在15分鐘內上墊一個圍棋隊。
And I want a go team assembled in 15 minutes on the pad.
需要多少時間？
How much longer?
我們降落在希思羅機場，然後我們會在菜刀。
We land at Heathrow, and then we're going on a chopper
在最後一站到維也納。
for the final leg to Vienna.
菜刀？
A chopper?
我還挺喜歡的噴氣。
I kinda like the jet.
在EMP一陣幾乎降至每架飛機從天空。
The EMP burst nearly dropped every plane from the sky
維也納左右，所以，為了我們自己的保護，
around Vienna, so, for our own protection,
我們切換到旅遊的一種形式。
we're switching to a form of travel
這是有點不太岌岌可危。
that's a little less precarious.
少岌岌可危？
A little less precarious?
放下你的武器！
Lower your weapons!
把'時間了！現在！
Put 'em down! Now!
去左邊。
Go to the left.
感動！
Move!
你休息的人，對我。
The rest of you men, on me.
這是遠遠不夠的，上校。
That's far enough, Colonel.
命令你的手下，放下他們的武器。
Order your men to lower their weapons.
放下你的武器，先生。
You lower your weapons, sir.
這是一種私有財產，因此。
This is a private property and therefore
你無權進入該設施。
you have no authority to enter this facility.
真的嗎？
Really?
我是美國陸軍指揮北約部隊。
I'm the United States Army commanding NATO forces.
我已經得到了權威的該死的空襲打電話。
I've got the authority to call in a damn air strike
在這棟樓，如果我想。
on this building if I wanted to.
你真的想要走這條道路？
You really want to go down that road?
你洛迪克，兒子。
You're out-gunned, son.
告訴你的導師把他們的武器下來。
Tell your men to put their weapons down
沒有人會受到傷害。
and no one gets hurt
好吧。
Alright.
因此，誰負責這個設施的？
So, who's in charge of this facility?
這將是我。
That would be me.
上校貝利，我承擔？
Colonel Bailey, I assume?
我很害怕，先生，
I'm afraid, sir,
有將是指令的變化。
that there's going to be a change of command.
這是一個私人研究機構。
This is a private research facility
由哈登企業全資，
wholly owned by Hadden Enterprises,
這是我所全資擁有的私人公司，。
which is a private company wholly owned by me.
它是什麼，先生。哈登，
What it is, Mr. Hadden,
是未經授權的電磁脈衝的部位。
is the site of an unauthorized electro-magnetic pulse.
我對北約授權。
I'm authorized by NATO
抓住這一獨資設施的控制。
to seize control of this wholly owned facility
直到我知道這到底是發生在這裏。
until I know what the hell is happening here.
我將提出正式投訴與歐盟。
I will be filing a formal complaint with the EU.
你這樣做，先生。
You do that, sir.
直到我聽到，否則，先生。哈登，
Until I hear otherwise, Mr. Hadden,
有一個在城裏有一個新警長。
there's a new sheriff in town.
所以這是最好的一個億萬富翁。
So this is the best a billionaire
能想出，是吧？
could come up with, huh?
一個古老的軍事風格的直升機？
An old military-style helicopter?
它們具有少得多的電子，這使得它們更安全飛行。
They have far less electronics, which makes them safer to fly
當你有問題，EMP 。
when you have problems with EMP.
這是非常令人欣慰。
That's very comforting.
西耶娜，我想知道。
Sienna, I was wondering...
什麼是霍頓的癡迷與水晶頭骨？
what's Hadden's obsession with the crystal skulls?
你要問他關於那個。
You need to ask him about that.
如果我有機會，我會。
If I get a chance, I will.
我們已經分手的消息在這裏。
We have breaking news here.
它剛剛被證實，所述電。
It has just been confirmed that the electrical
騷亂導致近停電。
disturbance that caused recent power outages
在西歐那樣，其實中心。
across western Europe did in fact center
從哈登行業研究機構。
from Hadden Industries research facilities...
。你可能還記得，哈登行業的老闆。
...As you may remember, the owner of Hadden Industries
是億萬富翁，威廉二世。哈登，
is billionaire, William S. Hadden,
一個人誰最近震驚華爾街。
a man who recently shocked Wall Street
當他決定賣掉他的所有美國利益的。
when he decided to sell all of his US interests
追求歐洲項目。
to pursue European projects...
。你可能還記得，隱藏的工具是一樣的設施。
...As you may recall, the Hadden facility is the same facility
與EMP爆炸了塗黑有關。
associated with the EMP blast that blacked out
大多數西歐。
most of western Europe.
我們正在等待一份官方聲明和評論。
We are awaiting an official statement and comments
從哈登的代表，
from Hadden representatives,
鑒於事件的性質，
given the nature of the incident,
上究竟發生了什麼。
on what exactly happened.
這是怎麼回事？
What's going on?
磁場生長。
The magnetic field is growing.
比前一個更快？
Faster than the last one?
指數。
Exponentially.
到底是什麼呢？
What the hell is this?
還有，我們可以做些什麼來控制反應沒有。
There's nothing we can do to control the reaction.
它打破。
It's breaking away.
可有人請解釋什麼，我在看什麼？
Can someone please explain what I am looking at?
這些來自世界各地聚集12水晶頭骨，
These are twelve crystal skulls gathered from around the world,
彙集首次。
brought together for the first time.
在神的名字是什麼，你說什麼？
What in God's name are you talking about?
我告訴你，那裏將是另一個。
I'm telling you that there's going to be another
電磁脈衝，比第1大。
electro-magnetic pulse, larger than the first one.
這些水晶頭骨產生的？
Generated by these crystal skulls?
是的。
Yes.
並沒有什麼我們可以做些什麼來阻止它。
And there isn't anything we can do to stop it.
嗯，我要去停止它。
Well I'm going to stop it.
武器自由，摧毀頭骨。
Weapons free, destroy the skulls.
上校，沒有。
Colonel, no.
上校，拜託了！
Colonel, please!
你不知道你在做什麼！
You have no idea what you're doing!
火！
Fire!
啊！ ！
Ahhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!
這到底是什麼？
What the hell was that?
某種電子脈衝油炸我們。
Some kind of electronic pulse fried us.
我認為，這個老菜刀保護呢？
I thought that this old chopper was protected from that?
導航系統有保護，
Navigation systems have protection,
但燃油泵，去年進行了更新。
but the fuel pumps were updated last year.
你沒有想到，當我們需要一把菜刀。
And you didn't think, that when we needed a chopper
與預售電子，即可能是一個問題？
with pre-sold electronics, that that might be an issue?
我們有沒有權力？
We've got no power?
我們在直升機。
We're in a helicopter.
我們將要墜落，像一塊石頭從天上。
We're going to fall like a stone from the sky.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
我們可以自動旋轉。
We can auto-rotate.
自動什麼？
Auto-what?
菜刀就像飛機。
Choppers are just like planes.
在上面的行為一樣，除了一個巨大的機翼的鋸片。
The blade on the top acts like a giant wing except
我們必須開始跳水，使這項工作，
we've got to start diving to make this work,
這是一個非常糟糕的地方，自動旋轉和土地。
and this is a really bad place to auto-rotate and land.
我們需要重新路由的電源，燃油泵。
We'll need to re-route the power to the fuel pump.
以及如何地獄我們要做到這一點？ ！
Well how the hell are we going to do that?!
好了，我們可以想辦法回到那裏。
Well, we can figure something out back there.
你知道如何做到這一點？
You know how to do this?
我們要找出其中的燃油泵。
We have to figure out where the fuel pump is.
多久，我們得到了，直到我們必須把這個東西了嗎？
How long have we got until we have to put this thing down?
以這樣的速度的下降，也許另一個兩分鐘，
At this rate of descent, maybe another two minutes,
但我們將不得不硬著陸。
but we're going to have a hard landing
在山的一側。
in the side of a mountain.
我發現了一個精靈。
I found a genie.
電力電纜。
Power cables.
我發現他們在這裏。
I found them right here.
燃油泵是在那裏。
Fuel pumps are up there.
把它放到這了這裏，看。
Put it into this up here, look.
這些燃料線在這裏？
These are the fuel lines here?
是啊。
Yeah.
我們不會以清除山脈！
We're not going to clear the mountain range!
我的工作是讓這兩個人回來，
My job is to get these two people back,
我們不拋棄！
we're not ditching!
得到它了？
Got it?
我們已經得到了發動機的動力又回來了！
We've got engine power back!
是的，不錯！
Yes, nice!
這是真棒！
That's awesome!
出色的工作，教授，優秀的！
Excellent work, professor, excellent!
我覺得他醒來。
I think he's waking up.
不錯的工作，你救貧混蛋。
Nice job, you save the poor bastard
我們得到的菜刀起來！
and we get the chopper up!
差不太多，如果我這樣說我自己！
Not too bad, if I say so myself!
不，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no!
哦，這只是輝煌，血腥的輝煌！
Oh, that's just brilliant, bloody brilliant!
無氣！
No gas!
你不裝燃油發電機？
You loaded a generator with no fuel?
對不起，先生。
Sorry, sir.
我閉嘴！
Just shut up!
我需要你-
I need you--
我要感謝你邀請我這個小小的冒險。
I want to thank you for inviting me on this little adventure.
Professor-
Professor--
移動。動，動了！ ！
Move. move, move!!!!!
你還好嗎？
You alright?
這是一個很好的方式，在歐洲到達。
That was a nice way to arrive in Europe.
是啊，你別客氣，教授。
Yeah, you're welcome, Professor.
現在我們已經找到交通工具前往維也納。
Now we've got to find transport to Vienna.
什麼是地獄剛剛發生了什麼？
What the hell just happened?
你試圖消滅他們。
You attempted to destroy them.
有沒有辦法將其刪除或銷毀。
There is no way to remove them or destroy them.
你現在明白了，上校？
Do you now understand that, Colonel?
我們仍然在線，先生。哈登。
We're still online, Mr. Hadden.
檢查冗余系統。
Check redundant systems.
先生，
Sir,
我是從直升機上接收信號。
I'm receiving a signal from the helicopter
運送醫生馬洛裏和溫斯頓。
transporting doctors Mallory and Winston.
什麼樣的信號？
What kind of signal?
緊急燈塔。
An emergency beacon.
菜刀下跌。
The chopper is down.
是否有任何傷亡？
Are there any casualties?
任何傷害？
Any injuries?
不知道，先生。
Don't know, sir.
該死！
Dammit!
他們一定的權利，通過脈衝飛行。
They must have flown right through the pulse.
坐上了失事地點的位置。
Get a location on the crash site.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
誰是這個菜刀？
Who was on this chopper?
西耶娜·馬洛裏，我的高級研究員，
Sienna Mallory, my senior researcher,
和約翰·溫斯頓。
and John Winston.
溫斯頓？教授約翰·溫斯頓？
Winston? Professor John Winston?
是的，上校。
Yes, Colonel.
他可能只是誰也阻止不了這個唯一一個。
He might just be the only one who can stop this.
但目前我只關注。
But presently my only concern
是懷念馬洛裏的幸福。
is for Miss Mallory's well-being.
我只是失去了四名士兵，先生。哈登。
I just lost four soldiers, Mr. Hadden.
我不是特別關心你的個人decadences 。
I'm not particularly concerned with your personal decadences.
西耶娜·馬洛裏是我的女兒，上校。
Sienna Mallory is my daughter, Colonel.
所以請，
So please,
使用你有什麼資源，在您的處置。
use whatever resources you have at your disposal
並讓他們在這裏盡快。
and get them here as soon as possible.
給我的男人的坐標，我會送回收隊伍。
Give my men those coordinates and I'll send a recovery team.
是的，先生。
Yes, sir.
先生。哈登，對不起。
Mr. Hadden, I'm sorry.
我是一個父親，以及。
I'm a father as well.
謝謝你，上校。
Thank you, Colonel.
道歉接受。
Apology accepted.
上校！你必須看到這個！
Colonel! You have to see this!
我剛在柏林的地方八國集團成員。
I've just arrived here in Berlin where members of the G8
現在收集了什麼似乎是一個緊急會議。
are now gathering for what seems to be an emergency meeting
對於這些奇怪的天氣現象。
regarding these strange weather phenomena
這似乎增加了每小時。
which seem to be increasing by the hour.
這樣的天氣phenomenahas現在已經達到臨界質量。
This weather phenomena has now reached critical mass
你可以看到，它現在已經成為一個巨大的漩渦！
as you can see, it's now become a massive vortex!
我剛剛收到突發新聞，軍事單位。
I've just received breaking news that the military units
現在已經轉移到城市，以協助疏散。
have now been moved into the city to assist with evacuation.
現在報道說。
Now reports say
一個閃電風暴兩倍大小。
that a lightening storm has tripled in size
在過去的24小時，
over the last 24 hours,
和巨漩渦現在席捲全市。
and that the giant vortex is now engulfing the city.
但隨著漩渦越飄過歐洲，
But as the vortex drifts farther across Europe,
我認為每個人的嘴唇問題是。
I think the question on everybody's lips is
我們在哪裏避難？
where do we evacuate to?
這是什麼？
What is this?
如果我是對的，這是結束的開始。
If I'm right, it's the beginning of the end.
不要採取這種錯誤的方式，
Don't take this the wrong way,
但我希望上帝你錯了。
but I hope to God you're wrong.
先生。哈登，我們別無選擇。
Mr. Hadden, we have no choice.
我們必須遏制實驗室和破壞頭骨。
We have to contain the lab and destroy the skulls.
那是不可能的，上校。
That is impossible, Colonel.
我們不能坐在這裏什麼都不做！
We can't just sit here and do nothing!
爸爸！
Daddy!
我以為我已經失去了你！
I thought I had lost you!
教授約翰·溫斯頓，
Professor John Winston,
我想你見見威廉·哈登。
I'd like you to meet William Hadden.
我的父親。
My father.
先生。哈登。
Mr. Hadden.
教授，我是你的父親是一個偉大的崇拜者，
Professor, I was a great admirer of your father's,
因為我是你自己。
as I am of you yourself.
這是上校貝利。
This is Colonel Bailey.
貝利。
Bailey.
教授。
Professor.
我很欣賞的客氣話，
I appreciate the kind words,
我不符合我的父親很多球迷。
I don't meet many fans of my father's
除了邊緣群體和狂人。
except for fringe groups and lunatics.
好了，我希望我沒有。
Well, I hope I'm neither.
之前，我失去了我的腿腳，
Before I lost my ability to walk,
這是在那裏我做了我最好的思想。
it was where I did my best thinking.
所以，如果你不介意的話，我們應該一起走？
So, if you don't mind, shall we walk together?
我不介意，如果你不介意的話解釋給我。
I don't mind at all, if you don't mind explaining to me
它究竟是什麼，我在這裏做。
what exactly it is that I'm doing here.
我是一個非常富有的人，醫生溫斯頓。
I'm a very wealthy man, Doctor Winston.
我一直在為我一生中最。
I have been for most of my life.
但是，我擔心我的傲慢已經得到了我的好。
But, I fear my hubris has gotten the better of me
在目前所發生的事情光。
in the light of what is now happening.
我會把它作為簡單的，我可以。
I'll put this as simply as I can.
你在這裏，醫生溫斯頓，因為我快死。
You're here, Doctor Winston, because I am dying.
我一直在與癌癥作鬥爭了十年。
I have been fighting cancer for ten years.
在我的追求治癒的，
In my pursuit of a cure,
我才知道水晶頭骨。
I became aware of the crystal skulls
並開始收購這些。
and began to acquire them.
所有的人，但第十三。
All of them but the thirteenth.
是的。
Yes.
第一個被發現在南美洲，
The first were found in South America,
接著是三個其他 -
followed by three others-
原諒我打斷了，先生，
Forgive me for interrupting, sir,
據我所知，歷史上。
I understand the history
但所有的頭骨已被證明是一個欺詐，
but all the skulls have proven to be a fraud,
碳定年測試了他們沒有老。
carbon dating has tested them to be no older
超過200或300年。
than 200 or 300 years.
相信我，我們有我們的失敗。
Trust me, we have had our failures.
沒有一個完美的。
No one's perfect.
讓我們只說測試是有些犯罪嫌疑人。
Let's just say the tests were somewhat suspect.
懷疑？
Suspect?
你在說什麼？
What are you saying?
碳定年是改變以某種方式？
The carbon dating was altered somehow?
你得到了十二種不同的頭骨。
You got the twelve different skulls
來自世界各個不同地區？
from all different pans of the world?
哈登行業擁有。
Hadden Industries owns
六個最大的碳年代測定設施。
six of the largest carbon dating facilities.
所以測試是假的？
So the tests were fake?
讓我們只說我們有證據更高的標準。
Let's just say we have a higher standard of proof.
啊，對吧。
Ah, right, right.
你欺騙了整個科學界。
You duped the whole scientific community.
我們所做的是softenthe收購價格。
What we did was soften the purchase price
把他們趕走館內陳列。
to take them off the museum displays.
先生。哈登可以成為億萬富翁，
Mr. Hadden may be a billionaire,
但每個人都有自己的價格。
but everyone has their price.
右，右。
Right, right.
所以它的錢。
So it's about money.
我們談論放在一起。
We're talking about putting together
12世界上最珍貴的對象。
twelve of the most precious objects in the world.
什麼，如果真不會發生。
Something that would not happen if the truth
成為眾矢之的。
became common knowledge.
先生。哈登，我不知道是什麼含義是。
Mr. Hadden, I don't know what the implications are
你改變這些試驗中，
of you altering these tests,
但我想它涉及監獄。
but I imagine it involves prison.
我要死了，上校。
I am dying, Colonel.
是啊，好了，你還沒死。
Yeah, well, you're not dead yet.
Ok了，堅持住，堅持住，堅持。
Ok, hold on, hold on, hold on.
沒有這個，現在真正重要的。
None of this really matters now.
頭骨是真實的。
The skulls are real.
所以他們多大？
So how old are they?
他們大多是過時大約50萬年前。
Most of them were dated about 500,000 years ago.
別人無法日期。
Others cannot be dated.
50萬年？
500,000 years?
那人早。
That pre-dates man.
這意味著一些其他來源。
Which implies some other origin.
也許是外星人？
Perhaps extraterrestrials?
先生。哈登，我不知道，如果你的碳約會有心計。
Mr. Hadden, I don't know if your carbon dating shenanigans
已導致這場災難，
have lead to this disaster,
但我知道，我還有一個問題。
but I do know that I have another problem.
防止全球的端。
Preventing the end of the world.
你和我有同樣的目標，上校。
You and I have the same goal, Colonel.
上校！
Colonel!
夠了！
Enough!
現在，如果你和教授溫斯頓能拿出一個解決方案，
Now if you and Professor Winston can come up with a solution,
我所有的耳朵。
I'm all ears.
但現在我必須賦予北約。
But now I must confer with NATO
並拿出我們自己的方法。
and come up with our own method.
蠻力將無法正常工作！
Brute force will not work!
你所看到的happenedwhen你的人試圖。
You saw what happened when your men attempted
攻擊的頭骨！
to attack the skulls!
他們有一個堅不可摧的領域身邊！
They have an impregnable field around them!
那是四個人。
That was four men.
我說的是一些藥更強。
I'm talking about some stronger medicine.
我們知道強行將不起作用。
We know force won't work.
會是怎樣？
What Will?
第十三頭骨。
The thirteenth skull.
但困境是。
But the dilemma is
我不知道從哪裏開始尋找它。
I have no idea where to begin to look for it.
我想你跟著你父親的腳步。
I want you to follow your father's footsteps
並發現它。
and find it.
滿足你的命運。
Fulfill your destiny.
先生。 hadden-
Mr. Hadden-
我的資源，每一個人。
Every single one of my resources
將在您的處置。
will be at your disposal.
上帝知道我創造了這個災難。
God knows I created this disaster.
如果非要用我的財富每一位來阻止它，
If I have to use every bit of my fortune to stop it,
這樣吧。
so be it.
有一件事，我們沒有一個有很大的。
There's one thing that neither one of us has much of.
而那會是什麼？
And what would that be?
時間。
Time.
所以我該承擔這個菜刀是比上一個更安全？
So am I to assume this chopper is safer than the last one?
這是冷戰技術。
It's Cold War technology.
它的建成能夠承受核爆炸。
It's built to withstand a nuclear explosion.
所以你為什麼不告訴我，哈登是你的父親嗎？
So why didn't you tell me that Hadden was your father?
和破壞的驚喜呢？
And spoil the surprise?
你知道，我們有很多共同點，教授。
You know, we have a lot in common, Professor.
真的嗎？
Really?
那是什麼？
What's that?
我們倆度過了我們的生活努力走出陰影。
We've both spent our lives trying to get out of the shadow
我們的父輩。
of our fathers.
是什麼馬洛裏是？
Is that what Mallory is?
這是我母親的娘家姓。
It was my mother's maiden name.
她去世時，我是一個小女孩。
She died when I was a little girl.
將它作出了區別，如果你已經知道我是誰嗎？
Would it have made a difference if you had known who I was?
什麼，我多麼認真了嗎？
In what, how seriously I took you?
或者多麼誘人我還以為你是當我們第一次見面？
Or how attractive I thought you were when we first met?
認真？
Seriously?
所以，你呃。
So, do you uh...
一直等到你的直升機拿到一個女孩獨自。
always wait until you get a girl alone in a helicopter
您胸圍之前這樣的行了呢？
before you bust a line like that out?
不，我通常等待，看看是否這個女孩我打的。
No, I usually wait to find out if the girl I'm hitting on
是億萬富翁的女兒。
is the daughter of the billionaire.
哦，肯定。
Oh, sure.
那麼我想這是一個恥辱。
Well then I guess it's a shame
我繼承被關押在生前信託。
that my inheritance is being held in a living trust.
啊。
Ahh.
所以我們要去哪裏？
So where are we going?
你爸爸告訴我，在我父親的後塵。
Your father told me to follow in my father's footsteps.
這就是我在做什麼。
That is what I'm doing.
第十三頭骨是在哪兒？
The thirteenth skull is down there?
不，這是我的父親來到了最後的地方。
No, this is the last place my father came
他消失前。
before he disappeared.
這是唯一的辦法了嗎？
And this is the only way down?
恐怕是。
I'm afraid so.
準備好了嗎？
Ready?
我們在這裏。
We're here.
方便，易於。
Easy, easy.
我得雅。
I've got ya.
這是有趣的。
That's interesting.
什麼？
What?
因為我在這裏與特裏，
Since I was here with Terry,
我發現這個洞穴已經崩潰。
I find that this cave has collapsed.
非常好？
That's good?
不，如果我們需要另一條出路。
Not if we need another way out.
或者我們可能避免這整個極限運動例行。
Or we could have avoided this entire extreme sports routine.
是的，脂肪的機會。來吧。
Yeah, fat chance. Come on.
你是怎麼得到你父親的筆記本電腦。
How did you get your father's notebook
如果他們從來沒有發現自己的身體？
if they never found his body?
這是送給我在一所大學在那裏我教。
It was sent to me at a college where I was teaching
你的父親在我面前解雇。
before your father had me fired.
OK，很好，沒有解釋是誰發送給你。
Ok, well that doesn't explain who sent it to you.
你不知道？
You don't know?
這是你的父親。
It was your father.
他送出一記隨之。
He sent a note along with it.
他說，他的研究人員的一個發現它。
He said that one of his researchers had found it
遠征，他覺得或許有一天。
on an expedition and he thought perhaps one day
我會覺得有用。
I would find it useful.
所以這是最後的地方你的父親是？
So this was the last place your father was?
這是在那裏他們發現了筆記本電腦？
This is where they found the notebook?
我傾向於同意你的。
I'd be inclined to agree with you.
但如果我父親的研究小組已經在這裏了。
But if my father's research team had already been here
他們沒有找到第十三頭骨，
and they didn't find the thirteenth skull,
我們為什麼在這裏？
why are we here?
持此，請。
Hold this, please.
這是我的父親來到了最後的地方。
This is the last place that my father came.
在我的弟弟失去了他的生活。
Where my brother lost his life.
和我打賭，答案還在這裏。
And I'm betting that the answer is still here.
我們只需要知道去哪裏找吧。
We just have to know where to look for it.
對不起，先生們。
Excuse me, gentlemen.
它是什麼？
What is it?
頭骨都產生了非常集中的磁場。
The skulls are generating a very focused magnetic field
它開始於隔離腔。
which begins in the isolation chamber
並伸出超出公用線。
and extends out beyond the common line.
這是分隔地球大氣層行。
That's the line that separates the Earth's atmosphere
來自外太空。
from outer space.
我知道它是什麼。
I know what it is.
似乎現在向後延伸到地球的核心。
It seems that it now extends back to the Earth's core.
什麼是地獄做所有的意思是，先生。哈登？
What the hell does all that mean, Mr. Hadden?
這意味著，現在有一個新的領域。
It means that there's now a new field
與現有的1競爭。
competing with the existing one.
好了，所以現在給我一個壞消息。
Alright, so now give me the bad news.
火山與地震活動，
Volcanic and seismic activity,
和良好的可能性，即地球的地殼鐵。
and a good possibility that the Earth's iron crust
會開裂就像一個雞蛋，
will crack like an egg,
如果這種情況發生全球將有字面上撕裂。
and if that happens the planet will be literally torn apart
而好消息嗎？
And the good news?
先生。普裏查德。
Mr. Pritchard.
以目前的速度，SAR，大約30小時。
At the current rate, sir, roughly 30 hours.
- 發出疏散令。 - 是的，先生。
- Issue an evacuation order. - Yes, sir.
在30小時，
In 30 hours,
我授權使用的戰術。
I am authorizing the use of a tactical
核武器在這個網站。
nuclear weapon at this site.
我會汽化那些神拋棄的東西。
I'll vaporize those god forsaken things
回到地方是，他們從來到。
back to wherever it is that they came from.
你所看到的所發生的當你的人試圖。
You saw what happened when your men attempted
消滅他們！
to destroy them!
這是四名士兵，先生。哈登。
That was four soldiers, Mr. Hadden.
我說的是力量尚未釋放。
I'm talking about power that hasn't been unleashed
自廣島。
since Hiroshima.
你要成為結束世界的男人。
You are going to be the man who ended the world.
也許它保存。
Or maybe saved it.
你還好嗎？
You alright?
嗯
Mmmhmm.
這邊。
This way.
做好。
Good job.
- 你還好嗎？ - 是啊。
- You ok? - Yeah.
約翰？
John?
看。
Look.
約翰，你還好嗎？
John, you ok?
是啊。
Yeah.
是啊，我很好。
Yeah, I'm fine.
這是給你的，我的兄弟。
This is for you, my brother.
我們已經準備好提取。
We're ready for the extraction.
繼續。
Go ahead
來吧！
Come on!
我們得離開這個地方！
We've gotta get out of this place!
是的，沒有開玩笑。
Yeah, no kidding.
來吧。
Come on.
我很高興，這是我們後面。
I'm glad that's behind us.
我們不需要這些了。
We don't need these anymore.
好。
Ok.
這裏，讓我幫你。
Here, let me help you.
好了，這邊。
Alright, this way.
我們走 ，來吧。
Let's go, come on.
直升機怎麼了？
What happened to the helicopter?
有人拍下來。
Someone shot it down.
誰？
Who?
我不知道。
I don't know.
大概誰開槍我在酒吧同一個人。
Probably the same person who shot at me in the bar.
他們加強它一個或兩個檔次。
They stepped it up a notch or two.
仔細。
Careful.
啊！
Agh!
你在幹什麼？那真痛啊！
What're you doing? That really hurt!
米切爾，你到底在這做什麼？
Mitchell, what the hell are you doing here?
哦，現在來吧。
Oh now come on.
你真的沒有想到先生。哈登。
You didn't really think Mr. Hadden
打算讓你在歐洲中途拖曳。
was going to let you traipse halfway across Europe
他珍愛的小女孩。
with his precious little girl
有沒有人讓你的眼睛，是不是？
with nobody to keep an eye on you, did you?
直升機怎麼了？
What happened to the helicopter?
有人用導彈把它打下來了。
Someone took it down with a missile.
有人似乎有意殺害我。
Someone who seems to be intent on killing me.
你能想到誰？
Do you have any idea who?
宗教狂熱分子，邊緣群體，
Religious fanatics, fringe groups,
- 白人至上主義者，中央情報局。 - 好吧，好吧。
- white supremacists, CIA... - Alright, alright.
你知道，我所知道的是，在我遇見你。
You know, all I know is that before I met you
我不知道，怎麼會有人想要殺我。
I had no idea that anyone would want to kill me.
我是一個十分討人喜歡的那種人。
I'm a likable enough kind of guy.
所以你說。你聽著，
So you say. Now look,
你想站在這兒，談談。
do you want to stand around here and talk about
誰是在你的刺客，
the assassins who are after you,
或者你想獲得地獄離開這裏。
or do you want to get the hell out of here
他們的工作之前，你是不是在菜刀。
before they work out that you weren't in the chopper
他們擊落？
that they shot down?
是啊，這就是我想。
Yeah, that's what I thought.
我想要一個EMP-屏蔽銅纜站在。
I want an EMP-shielded chopper standing by
拉我們其餘的人離開這裏到時候。
to pull the rest of us out of here when the time comes.
是的，長官。
Yes, sir.
他們將在這裏。
They'll be here.
我希望你是對的。
I hope you're right.
每個人的緣故。
For everyone's sake.
因為我不想名垂青史。
Because I don't want to go down in history
因為誰授權的核裝置的引爆的人。
as the man who authorized the detonation of a nuclear device
拯救世界。
to save the world.
那就不要做了，上校。
Then don't do it, Colonel.
這是從我手中。
It's out of my hands.
我們應該把這些燈出來，並殺死加熱器。
We should put these lights out and kill that heater.
它會吸引了錯誤樣的公司，
It could attract the wrong kind of company,
如果你知道我的意思。
if you know what I mean.
是啊，我冷，我們需要光算出這個。
Yeah, well I'm cold, and we need light to figure this out.
好，那你還不如送了一個信號彈。
Well, then you might as well send up a signal flare
並告訴誰是我們後，我們都。
and tell whoever is after us where we are.
也許你應該拿出你吸煙，廉價雪茄。
Maybe you should put out that cheap cigar you're smoking.
氣味會吸引了錯誤的那種人。
The smell will attract the wrong kind of people.
這是一個科伊巴。
It's a Cohiba.
哦，還有完善的。
Oh, well perfect.
在這種情況下，我會只吸引了。
In that case we'll only attract
最好的一種恐怖分子和刺客。
the best kind of terrorists and assassins.
此外，這就是為什麼我們有你在這裏。
Besides, that's why we have you here.
保護我們。
To protect us.
是啊，我不能保護你自己。
Yeah, well I can't protect you from yourselves.
它不是在這裏。
It's not here.
它必須是。
It has to be.
是啊，我還看不出來，我累了。
Yeah, well I can't see it and I'm tired.
也許我們應該抓住幾個睡眠時間。
Maybe we should grab a couple of hours of sleep.
重新開始。
Start fresh.
太陽將高達很快。
The sun will be up soon.
但是，如果我們不破解這個也沒什麼關係。
Although, if we don't crack this it won't matter.
如何我們該怎麼離開這裏沒有菜刀，米切爾？
How are we gonna get out of here without a chopper, Mitchell?
我不會把另外一隻小鳥在該地區。
I'm not putting another bird up in the area
直到我們確保它。
until we've secured it.
現在聽，教授。
Now listen, professor.
你需要專注於拯救世界。
You need to concentrate on saving the world.
我需要散散心，所以我能思考。
I need to get some fresh air so I can think.
去給他一隻手。
Go and give him a hand.
你看到了嗎？
You see it?
看什麼？
See what?
有。
There.
有啊！
There it is!
我知道我會找到它。
I knew I would find it.
讓我告訴你它在哪裏。
Let me show you where it is.
有你們兩個想通了？
Have you two figured it out?
是的，也許。
Yeah, maybe.
我需要報告的時間。哈登和上校。
I need to report to Mr. Hadden and the Colonel
如果你已經破解這個還是不。
if you've cracked this or not.
這不是地圖，這是地方。
This is not the map, this is the place.
這些，這些是地圖。
These, these are the map.
我不跟著你。
I'm not following you.
他們是明星。
They're stars.
此圖顯示的確切位置找到。
This drawing shows us exactly where to find
第十三頭骨。
the thirteenth skull.
我還以為你會興奮。
I thought you'd be excited.
好了，在洞穴寺廟必須是3000多年的歷史。
Well, the temple in that cave must be 3000 years old.
我說更像是5 。
I'd say more like five.
哦，甚至更好的。
Oh, even better.
所以我們要做的就是想通了。
So all we have to do is figure out
其中，該星座出現。
where that constellation appeared
在夜空中在5000年前？
in the night sky 5000 years ago?
嗯，這很容易。
Well, that's easy.
你知道，我知道，為了讓我們兩個。
You know, I realize that in order for the two of us
弄明白這將需要數月，甚至更長的時間。
to figure it out it would take months, maybe longer.
但對於你爸的超級計算機之一。
But for one of your dad's super computers
它應該是小菜一碟。
it should be a piece of cake.
正確的。
Right.
好吧，
Alright,
輸入偏角和推斷。
enter the declination and extrapolate.
哦，等等，我們已經得到的東西。
Oh wait, we've got something.
你們兩個是作品。
You two are a piece of work.
對了，你想知道的星座出現。
Right, you wanted to know where that constellation appeared
在夜空中在5000年前？
in the night sky 5000 years ago?
嗯，其實5302個月11天。
Well, actually 5302 months and 11 days.
有你的答案。
There's your answer.
這到底是什麼？
What the hell is that?
它的維索科山谷，這是理論上的一個金字塔。
It's the Visoko Valley, it's theoretically a pyramid.
這是我們要去的地方。
That's where we're going.
太陽金字塔
有趣的是它如何保持未開發。
It's interesting how it has remained unexplored
千百年來。
for thousands of years.
人們認為這是一個自然形成的很長一段時間。
People thought it was a natural formation for a long time.
哦，我的父親說，軍方把時鐘上我們。
Oh, my father said the military put a clock on us.
我們有六個小時。
We have six hours.
我希望米切爾世界末日前回來。
I hope Mitchell gets back before the world ends
和他出去想租一輛車。
and he's out trying to rent a car.
真的嗎？
Really?
這是一個有趣的選擇。
That's an interesting choice.
這是我們的人，這是我們的人！
That's our man, that's our man!
哦男孩。
Oh boy.
你為世界上最富有的人工作。
You work for the wealthiest man in the world
竟然租到最好的車是這樣的？
and the best car you could rent was this?
好了，對不起，王牌先生，但他們沒有用信用卡。
Well, excuse me, Mr. Trump, but they didn't take credit cards
這是所有我能得到的現金，我不得不。
and this was all I could get with the cash I had.
好了，讓我們去哪兒？
Well, so where are we going?
是這樣嗎？
Is that it?
你到底在期待，米切爾？吉薩？
What were you expecting, Mitchell? Giza?
好了，我不知道，也許更大的東西比？
Well, I don't know, maybe something bigger than that?
它只是看起來像一個奇怪形狀的小山。
It just looks like an odd-shaped hill.
好了，這是一個金字塔。
Well, it is a pyramid.
是啊，我知道，教授Smarty的褲。
Yeah, well I know that, Professor Smarty-Pants.
我要說它看起來並不像一個地方。
All I'm saying is it doesn't look like a place
將持有的關鍵，拯救世界。
that would hold the key to save the world.
我看到。
I see.
你期望什麼樣子？
And what do you suppose that would look like?
好了，好了，所以有什麼計劃？
Ok, alright, so what's the plan?
我們要保持低調，
We're gonna keep a low profile,
遠離村莊，直到天黑，
stay away from the village until it gets dark,
然後去好和安靜。
and then go in nice and quiet.
這個計劃聽起來強如在汽車的選擇。
That plan sounds as strong as the choice in cars.
坐進車內。
Get in the car.
我的天啊，還能再小嗎？
My goodness, could this be smaller?
哪裏是每個人？
Where is everyone?
我怎麼會知道？
How should I know?
一個鎮民大會，脫衣舞俱樂部？
A town meeting, strip club?
脫衣舞俱樂部？
Strip club?
這些都是很好的人。
These are nice people.
你永遠不知道。
You never know.
村莊都需要一個良好的脫衣舞俱樂部。
Villages all need a good strip club.
你不早說？
A little early, wouldn't you say?
好吧，我想我們都知道，每個人都。
Well, I guess we know where everyone is.
我們得出去。
We've got to get out.
- 這會過去，給它時間。 - 看看你身後。
- This will pass, give it time. - Look behind you.
哦，拍。
Oh, shoot.
出去。
Get out.
只是充當普通。
Just act normal.
不要東張西望。
Don't look around.
還沒有反應過來。
Don't react.
不要讓他們知道我們被跟蹤。
Don't make it known we're being followed.
但我們被跟蹤，所以我們怎麼行動？
But we are being followed, so how are we supposed to act?
休閒。
Casual.
究竟有多少？
How many are there?
還有我們兩個的後面，兩個在我們面前。
There's two behind us and two in front of us.
剛轉身打成一片。
Just turn around and mingle.
好的
QKEY
他們在做什麼？
What are they doing?
我以前見過你。
I've seen you before.
是的。
Yes.
我也見過你。
And I have seen you, as well.
現在，恐怕這將是我們最後一次見面。
Now, I'm afraid this will be our last meeting.
是，一些委婉的說法，因為你要殺死我們？
Is that some kind of euphemism because you're going to kill us?
放鬆，西耶娜。
Easy, Sienna.
不對抗的人。
Don't antagonize the man.
他有一把劍。
He's got a sword.
是的，這位教授有一個點。
Yeah, the professor has a point.
去，享受你的玩笑，因為它會現在都結束。
Go on, enjoy your banter, because it will all end now.
它是什麼，你呢？
What is it that you're after?
你知道我們是後。
You know what we're after.
你一直跟著我們。
You've been following us.
是的。
Yes.
這是我們的工作，保護第13個。
It is ourjob to protect the thirteen.
頭骨。
Skulls.
他們擁有不可思議的力量，當他們匯聚。
They possess incredible power when they are brought together.
一些你父親做了。
Something your father did.
你死之前，我想問問你。
Before you die, I wanted to ask you
你一旦發現你以為會發生什麼。
what it is you thought would happen once you found that
你求？
which you seek?
我們需要它阻止
We need to work together in order to stop it.
阻止什麼？
Stop what?
你不知道嗎？
Don't you know?
12頭骨所造成的破壞。
The destruction caused by the twelve skulls
正在匯聚。
being brought together.
我們需要第十三阻止它。
We need the thifleenth to stop it.
還有，如果一個人是愚蠢的，對這種力量。
Well, if a man was foolish enough to trifle
視如兒戲，
with this power,
那麼他會自我毀滅。
then it is he who has brought upon himself this destruction.
你不能拯救他們。
You cannot save them.
現在準備。
Now prepare.
約翰！
John!
不用擔心，看開點。
Don't worry, look away.
它只會花一秒鐘。
It'll only take a second.
住手！
Stop!
給我的劍。
Give me the sword.
你好，朱莉亞。
Hello, junior.
爸爸？
Dad?
我們埋葬了你。
We buried you.
我們以為你死了。
We thought you were dead somewhere.
對不起，兒子。
I'm sorry, son.
我們找了你這麼久，爸爸。
We looked for you for so long, Dad.
然後我發現你的日記。
And then I found your journal.
我把它在一個地方，我知道它會被發現。
I left it in a place I knew it would be discovered.
我曾希望，如果你發現了它，它會給你一些答案。
I had hoped if you found it, it would give you some answers.
它給了我答案，但目前更多的問題。
It gave me answers, but far more questions.
它基本上是什麼讓我在這裏。
It's basically what got me here.
發生了什麼事，爸爸？
What happened, Dad?
你去哪兒？
Where did you go?
我知道你有很多的問題，
I know you have a lot of questions,
你應該。
and you should.
我一直在第十三後頭骨了這麼多年，
I've been after the thirteenth skull for so many years,
我來了這麼近，
I had come so close,
然後我發現這個地方和兄弟會。
and then I found this place and the brotherhood.
這是兄弟會的最後一個據點。
This is the brotherhood's last stronghold.
它守住我們最後的秘密。
It holds the last of our secrets.
什麼樣的秘密？
What secrets?
我發現頭骨，約翰。
I found the skull, John.
它是真實的，就像我一直都知道這將是！
It's real, just like I always knew it would be!
他們給了我一個選擇。
They gave me a choice.
我可以死，
I could die,
或者我可以加入與他們。
or I could join with them
在保護頭骨的秘密。
in protecting the secrets of the skulls.
我已經尋找了這麼久，什麼也不在乎。
I had been searching so long, nothing else mattered.
顯然你不在乎你的家人。
Obviously your family didn't matter.
你的選擇導致你兒子死亡。
Your choice lead to your son's death.
泰利步你的後塵。
Terry died wanting to follow in your footsteps.
我愛你和你的兄弟比你永遠不會知道，
I loved you and your brother more than you will ever know,
但是這是我無法拒絕的。
but this was something I couldn't refuse.
一切後，我看到了，一切我已經學會了。
After everything I had seen, everything I had learned.
這是不是一種選擇，這是我的命運。
It wasn't a choice, it was my destiny.
也許你的命運，可以善加利用。
Maybe your destiny could be put to good use.
世界第十三頭骨，爸爸。
The world is the thirteenth skull, Dad.
你知道他們永遠不會讓你擁有它。
You know they will never let you have it.
不要讓泰利無謂的犧牲！
Don't let Terry's death be in vain!
沒有頭骨，數十億就會死亡。
Without the skull, billions will die.
如果頭骨已聚集，
If the skulls have been gathered,
和世界末日已經開始，就這樣吧。
and the end of the world has begun, so be it.
這是人的命運。
This is man's destiny.
人類的命運騎在你的肩膀。
Man's destiny rides on your shoulders.
你明白，他們不能永遠離開這個地方，現在。
You understand that they cannot ever leave this place now.
是的，我知道。
Yes, I know.
我只要求沒有看。
I only ask that I do not have to watch.
是的，我們不希望你心煩。
Yeah, we wouldn't want you to be upset
看你最後一個兒子被殺害你的命運！
watching your last son be killed for your destiny!
你會殺了我們這裏，在金字塔？
You're going to kill us here, in the pyramid?
你有沒有榮譽？
Do you have no honour?
女人，不跟我說話這個樣子！
Woman, do not speak to me like this!
我已經花了我的一生捍衛榮譽這個地方。
I have spent my life defending the honour of this place.
從未有紀念那些誰殺了，侯賽因！
There is never honour for those who kill, Hussein!
對不起，老朋友。
I'm sorry, old friend.
跟著我，這邊！
Follow me, this way!
沒有，先生，該中隊在空中待命。
No, sir, the squadron is in the air awaiting orders.
磁場是95％，先生。
The magnetic field is at 95 percent, sir.
這一次，我們讓所有人都離開這裏。
It's time we get everybody out of here.
上校，你的炸彈不會丟你認為他們會。
Colonel, your bombs aren't going to do what you think they will.
只要給他們更多的時間。
Just give them more time.
我給他們盡可能多的時間。
I'll give them as much time as I can.
在那之後，我下命令。
After that, I'm under orders.
謝謝。
Thank you.
如果我們每個人都生活那麼久再感謝我。
Thank me if we all live that long.
我們得離開這裏。
We've gotta get out of here.
米切爾，叫上我爸爸。
Mitchell, call my father.
爸爸，你在做什麼？
Dad, what are you doing?
這個地方是我的生命，約翰。
This place is my life, John.
我無處可去。
I have nowhere to go.
讓我死在這裏。
Let me die here.
對兄弟會所做的我不值得活。
I don't deserve to live after what I did to the brotherhood.
你在說什麼？
What're you talking about?!
現在你有不同的生活，
You have a different life now,
你已經有了一個孫女！
you've got a granddaughter!
我有一個孫女？
I have a granddaughter?
沒錯！泰利的女兒！她馬上7歲了！
Yes! Terry's daughter! She's going to be seven!
真的嗎？ 是的！
Really? Yes!
爸爸！
Dad!
對不起，兒子。
I'm sorry, son.
爸爸，不！
Dad, no!
來吧，我們必須去。
Come on, we have to go.
約翰，加油！現在！
John, come on! Now!
- 爸爸！ - 來吧，約翰，現在！
- Dad! - Come on, John, now!
主席先生，磁場達到100％。
Sir, the magnetic fields are at 100 percent.
我怕你的人都出來的時候，先生。哈登。
I'm afraid your people are out of time, Mr. Hadden.
阿爾法中隊，時間目標？
Alpha Squadron, time to target?
複製。
Copy that.
8分鐘。
Eight minutes.
我們必須讓每個人都出在一個安全的最小距離。
We've got to get everyone out at a safe minimum distance
前引爆。
before detonation.
你聽說過他們，他們是在他們的途中！
You heard them, they're on their way!
我已經給了他們足夠的時間，我可以，先生。哈登。
I've given them as much time as I can, Mr. Hadden.
我們不能再等下去了。
We can't wait any longer.
- 我們在這裏完成。 - 是的，先生。
- We're finished here. - Yes, sir.
爸爸！
Daddy!
我告訴你，他們會做吧。
I told you they'd make it.
我不是回顧炸彈。
I'm not re-calling the bombs
直到我敢肯定這件事情的作品。
until I'm certain this thing works.
讓我們這樣做之前，為時已晚。
Let's do this before it's too late.
西裝應該保護你從光。
The suit should protect you from the light.
它限制你接觸到的任何電離輻射，
It limits your exposure to any ionizing radiation,
但我不能做出任何承諾。
but I can't make any promises.
我真的不知道發生了什麼，
I don't actually know what's happening,
但似乎漩渦正在消退。
but it seems that the vortex is dissipating
和風暴似乎即將結束！
and the storm seems to be coming to an end!
約翰。
John.
哦，謝謝。
Oh, thanks.
我認為，我們需要喝一杯。
I think we need to get a drink.
當我說我們我的意思是我。
And when I say we I mean me.
這是你的回合，教授。
It's your round, professor.
你怎麼了，先生？
Are you ok, sir?
叫我的醫生。
Call my doctor.
馬上，先生。
Right away, sir.
- 上校。 - 是嗎？
- Colonel. - Yes?
如果你能可能幫助我的東西。
If you could possibly help me with something...
如果我可以。
lf l can.
關鍵九基地，我們準備好了。
Key Nine to Base, we're ready.
好吧，密封腔。
Alright, seal the chamber.
收到。
Copy that.
結束了。
It's over.
現在怎麼辦？
What now?
等下。
One second.
她的父親已經死了。
Her father is dead.
西耶娜，我很抱歉。
Sienna, I'm so sorry.
沒關係，我想我知道這遲早要來。
It's ok, I guess I knew it was coming
我只是不知道什麼時候。
I just didn't know when.
我明白。
I understand.
我猜你做的，
I guess you do,
比其他人多。
more than anyone else.
CMV剛剛得知神秘的億萬富翁。
CMV has just learned that mysterious billionaire
威廉·哈登已經去世。
William Hadden has died.
它不知道哈登先生確切死亡時間，
It is not known exactly when Mr. Hadden passed,
但他的發言人說是上周某個時間。
but his representatives say that it was some time last week.
不是因為霍華德·休斯已經有這麼多的奧秘。
Not since Howard Hughes has there been so much mystery
周圍的億萬富翁死亡。
surrounding the death of a billionaire.
粗譯:賈寶玉是我龜孫子